BACKEND SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Nahuel Brandán

EMAIL: contact@nahuelbrandan.com | WEB: www.nahuelbrandan.com

ABOUT ME

Backend Software Developer, specialized in the **Python** ecosystem, with more than **3 years** of experience in the industry.

I am passionate about turning ideas into functional products through software, going through the different stages of development and promoting good practices. Always in constant learning.

EXPERIENCE

BACKEND SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Company: Satellogic | 06/2022 - 09/2022

Company specialized in earth observation satellites. Design, manufacture, and operate his own fleet of satellites.

I was part of the backend development team, based on Python, of satellite flight applications, dealing with **highly complex problems**.

Company: Ascentio Technologies | Project: Sabia-Mar | 08/2021 - 05/2022

Sabia-Mar is a satellite mission, with advanced technology for the study of the sea and the ocean.

I worked as a software developer in **Python**, making contributions to different communication and flight planning modules of the satellite. Developer of both the software and the validation **tests**. Working with technologies like: **Robot Framework**, **Docker**, **FastAPI**, **Django**, **APIs**.

Company: IncluIT | **Project: Junar** | 03/2019 - 07/2021

- Performing development activities in Python + Django + Django Rest Framework.
- Integration of Autho and Keyclok as a security layer to an API Management.
- Development related to **Elastic Search**, **Redis**, **Celery**.

EDUCATION (

BACHELOR'S DEGREE IN COMPUTER ANALYST

Faculty of Mathematics, Astronomy, Physics and Computing - UNC | 10/2018

Career with strong emphasis on programming, analysis and design of systems, databases and computer networks, without neglecting the theoretical aspects that sustain them.

SELF-STUDY ONLINE COURSES | Platzi | 01/2021 - Present

More than **100** courses completed and in constant learning in the Platzi professional online academy, on various topics such as: soft skills, english, software development, finance.

SKILLS (

- Programming languages: Python, C.
- Databases: MySQL, MongoDB, Redis, Elastic Search.
- Frameworks: **Django**, **FastAPI**, **Robot FW**.
- Others: Linux, API Rest, Django, Git, Bash, Autho, Docker, FastAPI, Robot FW.

EXTRAS (

• English: B1 intermediate.

• Spanish: Native.







